原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译     屯栗子  苏小黛  TracyOY  glida
翻译     kathy567  海云生  C·A  Giggles
校对     幽冥部落  TracyOY
时间轴   觉得T-1000最牛の查   Ans
时间轴   紫夏   没有影子   啾
后期     渔夫
总监     布塔
像是一个巨大的闪光灯
It's like a giant strobe light...
烧穿了我的双眼
burning right through my eyes.
但不知道为什么我还能看得见
Somehow I can still see.
孩子们像烧焦的纸片
Children look like burnt paper...
黑漆漆的
black...
一动不动
not moving.
接着爆炸产生的冲击波击中他们
And then the blast wave hits them.
他们就像树叶一样四处飞散
And they fly apart like leaves.
关于世界末日的梦是很常见的
Dreams of the end of the world are very common.
根本不是梦  蠢货  是真实的场景
It's not a dream, you moron. It's real.
我知道发生的日期
I know the date it happens.
我相信你的感受确实很真实
I'm sure it feels very real to you.
1997年8月29日
On August 29th, 1997,
你他妈也会觉得非常真实的
it's gonna feel pretty fuckin' real to you, too!
谁要是没涂两百万的防晒霜
Anybody not wearing two million
那天都会惨不忍睹
sunblock is gonna have a real bad day.
-明白吗  -莎拉
- Get it? - Sarah...
天呐  你觉得自己活得很安全吗
God, you think you're safe and alive?
你们已经死了  所有人
You're already dead. Everybody.
他  你  你们都死了
Him, you! You're dead already!
这个地方  全都不存在了
This whole place, everything you see is gone!
你他妈才是活在梦里
You're the one living in a fucking dream!
因为我知道这事确实发生过  发生过
'Cause I know it happened! It happened!
曾经有这样一个未来
There once was a future
人类被会思考的机器
in which humankind was hunted...
以及为杀戮而生的终结者
by a machine that could think...
追捕猎杀
and Terminators built to kill.
一个毫无希望的未来
A future without hope.
危地马拉利文斯顿  1998年
但那种未来没有发生  因为我阻止了它
That future never happened because I stopped it...
为了保护我的儿子
to protect my son...
也为了拯救人类
and to save us all.
不
No!
扫描模式25784
目标分析
栅格精度
目标匹配
编号342-589
任务资料
康纳  约翰
面部
目标已终结
不
No.
No!
我曾经拯救了三十亿生命
Once I saved three billion lives...
约翰
John!
但却救不了我的儿子
but I couldn't save my son.
约翰
John!
一个机器从我身边夺走了他
A machine took him from me.
也终结了我
And I am terminated.
终结者
黑 暗 命 运
墨西哥城
22年后
天呐
我知道
我也有这种感觉
你就打算坐在那里吗
快过去
她还活着
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我们拿她怎么办
我也不知道
该死
站住别动
别动
警官
我们只是想帮助这位女士
你朋友怎么了
我不知道
我们都不认识她
好了  好了  好了
Okay, okay, okay.
别碰我
你们给她嗑了什么
没有
她是从桥上掉下来的
当然了
最好是
天上掉裸体美女这种事我喜欢
走吧
放开他
天啊
太厉害了吧
谢谢你  女士
Thanks, lady.
你刚才救了我们
You just saved our asses.
先别着急谢我
Don't thank me yet.
去死吧  女人
行了  走吧
"我们帮帮她"  "她受伤了"  都是你说的
早上好  莫娜
总是带着花
总是
要玉米粽吗
好的  我给迭戈带一个
我能顺块芒果吗
当然
早上好
弟弟  早啊
Hey, little brother. Good morning.
我带了玉米粽和玉米粥
I brought tamales and atole.
好香
快看这个
147个赞
我很快就能超过布鲁诺·马尔斯了
如果想在美国成为大人物  该怎么说
Well, if you want to be big in America, you would say...?
我会超过布鲁诺·马尔斯
I'm going to pass Bruno Mars...
很快
pronto?
很好
Good.
-走吧  -好的
- Let's go. - Okay.
塔科
你觉得这件怎么样
好不好看
我把早饭放桌上
记得中午去看医生
别小题大做了  达妮
你怎么这么顽固
我天生就是这样的
现在改变你不觉得晚了吗
-玉米饼很好吃  -谢谢
爸爸
早啊
走吧  迭戈  我们要迟到了
Let's go, Diego. We're running late.
去吧  儿子
别忘了
知道了
回来的时候买点鸡蛋
你说了算
拜拜  塔科
茱莉亚  我正在想你
你都想了什么
很抱歉
我得走了
我姐姐...
-我刚刚在把妹  -是啊
- I had something going there. - Yeah.
-我看到了  -拜托
- I saw it. - Come on.
你觉得我撩的太过火了吗
You think I was flirting with her too much?
我觉得你一开口就让人受不了
I think all the parts where you were talking were too much.
很好笑
Funny.
早上好
塔科  安静点
什么事
早上好
有什么事吗
我找达妮娜·拉莫斯
我是她朋友
是吗
真奇怪
她朋友都叫她达妮
达妮
Dani?
没错  确实是
亚流汽车厂
早上好
我的工位上来了个新人
There's a new guy at my station.
我看到了
I see that.
机器人
Robot.
真酷
桑切斯先生  怎么回事
Senor Sanchez, what's going on?
未来
迭戈
Diego...
克雷格让你去办公室见他
好
Si.
我去
I'll go.
-去我的工位  -不不不
- Take my spot. - No, no, no.
他要见的不是你
我知道
打扰一下  先生
什么事
我家孩子又忘带午饭了
达妮·拉莫斯
Dani Ramos.
比赛怎么样
How's the game?
规矩很清楚  朋友
头盔和背心不能少
你穿成这样可不能进去
绝对不行
我明白了
拜托了  格拉蒙德先生  他可是我弟弟
Please, Mr. Grummond. It's my brother.
可是达妮  他又不是你
But, Dani, he ain't you.
接下来呢
What's next?
外面有三千个人
3,000 people out there.
如果我告诉他们
What happens if I tell them
他们随时会被机器取代  会有什么后果
they're just keeping a spot warm for some machine?
你爸怎么来了
你怎么来了  爸
你们又忘带午饭了  儿子
达妮已经帮我们打包好午饭了
达妮呢
她在跟老板谈话
他们要用那破机器取代我
她什么时候回来
我不知道
她来了
那不是你父亲
That is not your father.
那是个机器  而且是被派来杀你的
That is a machine that was sent here to kill you.
-放开我  -跟我走
- Let me go! - You come with me
否则不出三十秒你就会死
or you're dead in the next 30 seconds.
快走
Come on.
怎么回事
你是谁
Who are you?
我是救你命的人
I'm the person saving your life.
达妮
Dani!
快走  达妮
Go, Dani.
躲在我身后
Stay behind me!
女士  闪开
Hey, lady!
格雷丝
Grace.
我叫格雷丝
My name is Grace.
那样杀不死它
That won't kill it.
-我们得走了  快  -什么
- We gotta go. Move! - What?
-快走  -迭戈
- Go! - Diego!
去哪
To where?
走就是了
Keep going!
快来
Come on!
这边  走这边
Here. This way.
快
Come on!
拜托
Please!
能告诉我们那东西是什么吗
Can you tell us what that thing is?
那是个终结者  Rev-9型
It's a Terminator. A Rev-9.
他是从未来派过来的  我也是
He was sent here from the future. I was, too.
上车
Get in.
快上车
Get in!
你也是机器吗
Are you a machine, too?
不  我跟你们一样是人类
No, I'm human like you.
可你的手臂...
But, uh, your arm...
我是强化人
I'm augmented.
什么  强化人
What? Augmented?
妈的  该死
Fuck! Shit!
糟了
Oh, shit.
不
No!
快点  再开快点
Faster! Go faster!
我知道你很害怕  但我是来保护你的
I know you're scared, but I am here to protect you.
为什么是我们
Why us?
是你  达妮  你是我的任务
You, Dani. You're my mission.
我
Me?
不行  不行
No, no, no!
小心
Look out!
快点  再快点
Go faster! Go faster!
操
Fuck!
检查引擎
不  不
No! No!
天啊
Oh, my God!
不
No!
你来开
Drive!
-什么  -你会开车吗
- What? - Can you drive?
-不  我不会  -我会  我会
- No, I mean, I can't... - I can! I can!
好吧
Yeah.
-稳住  -格雷丝
- Hold it. - Grace...
达妮  系好安全带
Dani, put your seat belt on.
迭戈
Diego...
你还好吗
没事
我没事
格雷丝  帮帮我
Grace! Help me!
迭戈受伤了
It's Diego!
拜托  把他弄出去
Please! Take him out.
达妮
Dani.
我无能为力
I can't.
什么  不
What? No, no!
别  他会失血过多的
Don't. He will bleed out.
你没事吧
先生
Senor?
迭戈
Diego.
-达妮  我们得走了  -我是不会丢下他的
- Dani, we have to go. - I'm not leaving him.
带她走  保护好她
Take her. Save her.
-不  -抱歉了
- No! - I'm sorry.
求你了
Please!
不
No.
-迭戈  -达妮
- Diego! - Dani!
达妮  达妮  够了
Dani! Dani, stop!
你为什么要那么做
Why did you do that?
我们得走了  不然他就白死了
We have to go, or he died for nothing.
-不  -快走
- No. - Come on.
迭戈
Diego!
该死
Oh, shit.
等他们开始杀我时  你就跑
When they start to kill me, run.
什么
What?
我马上就回来
I'll be back.
那他妈是谁
Who the fuck is that?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我们得赶紧走了
But we have to move.
快走
Go.
我们不能就这么...
We can't just...
-这是那个女士的车  -你不走它就会杀了你
- Grace, it's that lady's car. - Dani, you go or it kills you.
就这么简单
It's that simple.
王八蛋
Son of a bitch!
达妮
Dani...
我要喝水
I need some water.
后面可能有
If we can maybe look in the back.
我想回家
I wanna go home.
带我回家
Take me home.
不行
We're not doing that.
我得把迭戈的事告诉爸爸
I have to tell my father about Diego.
做不到
It's not possible.
他还不知道迭戈的事
He doesn't know about Diego.
我得见我爸
I need to see my father!
你爸已经死了
Your father is dead.
什么
What?
复制人类需要进行身体接触
It needs physical contact to copy people.
被复制的人活不下来
And they don't survive.
不
No.
你怎么了
What's wrong with you?
我要崩溃了
I'm crashing.
你身上滚烫
You're burning up.
我的新陈代谢只适合短暂的爆发
My metabolism was tuned for short, intense bursts.
要么在几分钟内阻止终结者
You either stop a Terminator in the first few minutes...
要么就会死
or you're dead.
我需要药
I need meds.
格雷丝
Grace!
醒醒
Wake up!
你要去哪
Where are you going?
回到车上来
Get back in the car.
我得保护你
I have to protect you.
你连路都走不了
You can't even walk.
我要去找警察
I'm going to the police.
你找警察  它就会找到你
You do that, it'll find you.
你找一百个警察来对抗终结者
You put a hundred cops between you and a Terminator...
一百个警察都会死
you'll get a hundred dead cops.
达妮  拜托
Dani, please.
等等  来后面
Wait. Come here.
-你说你不会开车的  -是的
- You said you can't drive. - Yeah.
我边开边学
I'll figure it out.
格雷丝  格雷丝
Grace, Grace!
没事了  我们到了
It's okay. We're here.
我靠  你还真重
Fuck, you're heavy.
我们到了
We're here.
格雷丝
Grace.
小姐  你需要帮助吗
我们没事  谢谢
来人啊
需要帮...
我需要抗癫痫药
I need any anticonvulsant.
聚苯乙烯磺酸钠  胰岛素  苯二氮平
Sodium polystyrene sulfonate, insulin, benzodiazepine...
你有医生处方吗
Do you have a doctor's prescription?
这就是我的处方
Here's my prescription.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
去他妈的
Fuck it.
让开
Move.
非常抱歉  有人要杀我们
没关系
It's okay.
格雷丝
Grace.
Grace?
格雷丝
Grace.
让我帮你们吧
好吧
我救了你们的命
I save your ass...
你们却偷了我的车  真行啊
and you steal my truck. Nice.
我...
I...
算了  车都废了
Never mind. It's burnt.
她怎么了
What's wrong with her?
我不知道
I don't know.
她是病了还是怎么的
She's sick or something.
我要找你俩问清楚情况
Well, I need answers from you two.
我们把她抬上车吧
So let's get her in the car.
把枪给我  免得你伤到自己
Give me that before you hurt yourself.
那你是谁
So, who are you?
我是达妮娜·拉莫斯
Um, Daniella Ramos.
达妮
Dani.
谁都不是
I'm nobody.
达妮  你肯定很重要  不然他们也不会派...
Well, Dani, you must be somebody, or they wouldn't have sent...
她这样的来保护你
whatever she is to protect you.
你有手机吗
Hey, you got a phone?
-有啊  -能给我看一下吗
- Yes. - Could I see it for a sec?
搞什么鬼啊
你还不如戴个跟踪手环呢
Might as well be wearing a tracking bracelet.
等我准备好要干掉那个东西时
When I'm ready to kill that thing,
我自然会让它知道我们的位置
then I'll let it know where we are.
应该用浴缸才对
We should have done this in the bathtub.
那你看到哪里有浴缸了吗
Have you seen the bathtub?
我把我的手机装在薯片袋里
I keep my cell phone in the chip bag.
铝箔能阻隔GPS信号
The foil blocks the GPS signal
这样他们就无法追踪到我了
so they can't track me.
谁在追踪你
Who's trying to track you?
我在几个州被通缉了
I'm wanted in a couple of states.
其实是50个州
50, actually.
但为什么要十包呢
But why 10 bags?
因为我特别爱吃薯片
Because I really like potato chips.
她的药
Her meds...
你怎么知道每一种需要多少剂量
how do you know how much of each to use?
我不知道
I don't.
没人会知道他是谁
No one will know who he is.
你说谁
Who?
我弟弟
My brother.
当时他在车里...
He was in the truck when...
谁能让他  还有我爸
Who will be there to bury him?
入土为安
Or my father?
没有葬礼
No funerals.
没人跟他们道别
No one there to say goodbye.
葬礼救不了他们
Funerals don't help them.
道别也帮不了你
And goodbyes don't help you.
你只能学着接受这一切
You just have to learn to live with it.
呼叫基地
Come in, base.
这里是蜻蜓三号  请求近距空中支援
This is Dragonfly Three requesting close air support.
我们在五公里外
We are five klicks out,
运送重要伤员  完毕
carrying wounded precious cargo. Over.
收到  蜻蜓三号
Roger that, Dragonfly Three.
请注意五号方位有敌人靠近
Be advised there are hostiles inbound on vector five.
抢救小组
The trauma crew is standing
在南侧隧道等候指挥官
by for the commander at the south tunnel.
Rev-7型在追击我们  随意开火
We have Rev-7s in pursuit. Weapons free.
我们走
Let's move!
我们有三十秒
We got 30 seconds.
-马上下来  回撤  -快
- Get off there now! Move back! - Go!
敌人来袭
Incoming!
你把指挥官带进去
You get the commander inside.
是
Okay.
你们三个  跟我来  拖住它们
You three, with me! Hold them back!
快
Come on!
小心
Look out!
我们寡不敌众  需要立刻增援
We're being overrun! We need reinforcements now!
掩护她
Cover her!
让开  进来了
Move! Coming in!
靠
Shit!
她多处被刺伤
She's got multiple stab wounds.
胸部创伤严重
A lot of chest trauma here.
赶快将这些伤口缝合
Let's get these holes sealed up.
在右侧插入胸管
Get a chest tube in the right side.
这下会疼得你想骂娘
This is gonna hurt like a motherfucker.
等等  等下
Wait, wait.
不
No!
-插好了  -不  不
- Here. - No, no!
我得保护你们的指挥官
I need to protect your commander.
幸亏有你  指挥官现在安全了
The commander is safe, thanks to you.
别担心  士兵  你能挺过去
Don't worry, soldier. You'll make it.
我自愿
I volunteer.
将我变成强化人
Make me an Augment.
胸骨正中切口  胸骨柄切开
Midline sternotomy with manubrial splitting.
肺部压缩  心脏定位
Lung deflation and cardiac localization.
好了  我们开始吧
Okay, let's gear up.
莎拉
Sarah?
说话
Talk.
快说
Talk fast.
你先说
You first.
放开我
Get off me.
莎拉
Sarah!
莎拉  开门
Hey, Sarah! Open the door.
达妮
Dani!
-你还好吗  -没事  你呢
- You okay? - Yeah, you okay?
挺好
Yeah.
怎么回事
What happened?
把我锁在屋子外面
Locked me out of the room?
有时候家长要讨论大人的事情
Sometimes mommies and daddies have to have grown-up discussions.
那么你是来保护她的
So you're here to protect her.
你是个什么东西
What are you?
以前从没见过像你这样
Never seen one like you before.
几乎就和人类一样
Almost human.
我就是人类
I am human.
只不过是强化了
Just enhanced.
速度更快  力量更强
You know, increased speed and strength,
微型钍反应堆
thorium micro-reactor.
也就是说你要是惹毛我了
Which means I can rip your throat out
我能一把掐死你  所以别惹我
if you piss me off, so don't.
你从哪个年代来的
When are you from?
2042年
2042.
该你说了
Your turn.
我叫莎拉·康纳
My name is Sarah Connor.
我和她差不多年纪的时候
When I was about her age...
一个终结者被派来杀我
a Terminator was sent to kill me...
阻止我的儿子约翰出生
to stop the birth of my son, John.
反抗军的首领
Leader of the Resistance.
哪个反抗军
Which resistance?
人类反抗军
The human resistance.
跟天网对抗的那个
Against Skynet?
那个要消灭全人类的人工智能
The AI that's trying to wipe us all out?
我从没听说过
I've never heard of it.
很好
Good.
是约翰和我改变的
John and I changed that.
我们改变了未来
We changed the future.
拯救了三十亿人类
Saved three billion lives.
不用谢
You're welcome.
你的儿子现在在哪
Where's your son now?
天网派了好几个终结者追杀他
Skynet had sent several Terminators to hunt him.
其中一个最终找到了我们
One finally caught up with us and...
执行了来自没有发生的未来的命令
carried out orders from a future that never happened.
从那以后
Since then...
我就在猎杀终结者
I hunt Terminators.
整日喝酒到不省人事
And I drink till I black out.
这样的自我介绍够了吗
Enough of a resume for you?
不够
No.
你怎么知道我们会上那条高速
How did you know we'd be on that freeway?
面试结束  我们该动身了
Interview's over. We gotta move.
我们
We?
"我们"是不存在的
There is no "We."
达妮是和我一起的  保护她是我的任务
Dani's with me. It's my mission to protect her.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
结果如何呢
How's that working out for you?
显然你对这个时代的了解还不够
Clearly you don't know everything about this time.
每个带手机的人都是行走的传感器平台
How anyone with a phone is a walking sensor platform.
每个十字路口  每个加油站
How every intersection, every gas station
每个便利店都有摄像头
and 7-Eleven has cameras.
这个世界上的每个人都会在
Nobody walks through this world
两公里范围内留下数码痕迹
without leaving a digital trail a mile wide.
我猜那个追杀她的终结者
And my guess is that Terminator hunting her...
可以随时获取那些数据
can access that data anytime.
你俩是撑不过十小时的
You two won't last 10 hours.
我们把话说明白
Let's get something straight.
如果你让她陷入危险  或者碍着我了
If you put her in danger or you get in my way,
我就搞死你
I will fuck you up.
好
Right.
我来开车
I drive.
那个机器...
So, that machine...
谁派来的
who sent it?
不知道对方什么来头  我就没法对付它
I can't fight it if I don't know what we're up against.
是终结者Rev-7型
It's a Rev-9 model.
你对付不了
You don't fight it.
只能逃跑
You run from it.
好吧  但是什么人派来的
Yeah, but who sent it?
不是什么人
Not who.
而是什么东西  而且不是
What. And it wasn't some...
天网那东西
Skynet thing.
在真正发生的未来里
In the future that actually happened...
它叫"军团"
it's called Legion.
军团
Legion.
为网络战争打造的人工智能
An AI built for cyber warfare.
那些混蛋真是不长教训
Those assholes never learn.
它展开了攻击
And it attacked.
-攻击谁  -我们
- Attacked who? - Us.
每个人  人类
Everybody. Humanity.
莎拉  你怎么知道我们会在那架桥上
Sarah, how did you know we would be on that bridge?
我会收到信息
I get these texts.
精准坐标定位  日期  时间  精确到秒
Precise GPS coordinates, dates, times, down to the second.
这些信息结尾都会有出现四个字
They always end with the same two words.
"为了约翰"
"For John."
所以我就带上所有武器
So I pack up every weapon I've got,
去定位的地方  干掉任何惹我的人
and I head to those coordinates to kill whoever is messing with me.
有个停车场上的空气被撕裂
The air splits open above a parking lot
然后一个终结者掉了出来
and a Terminator drops out.
我把它摧毁了
So I destroy it.
然后过了两年  同样的事
And then two years later, same thing.
位置  时间  日期  "为了约翰"
Location, time, date, "For John."
我把那个也干掉了
I frag that one, too.
上周我收到两条信息
And last week, I get two texts,
都在墨西哥城
both in Mexico City.
你查到是谁发的信息了吗
Did you ever find out who sends those texts?
没有  信息总是加密过的
No. They're always encrypted.
信息还在你手机上吗
Do you still have them on your phone?
达妮
Dani.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
未来技术
Future shit.
怎么了  怎么回事
What's wrong? What is it?
这些信息是从拉雷多市郊发出的
These texts came from outside Laredo.
两天前
Two days ago,
我的指挥官让人在我身上纹了这个坐标
my commander had them tattoo these coordinates on me.
好像我记不住似的
As if I couldn't remember shit.
告诉我要是任务出了岔子就去这里
Told me to go here in case anything went sideways with my mission.
这个地方就是给你发信息的位置
It's the same location your texts come from.
给你发信息的人
Whoever sent you these texts
就是他们让我求助的人
is the same person I was told to go to for help.
什么意思
What does it mean?
意思是我们要去德州了
It means we're going to Texas.
你要和一个没有签证的墨西哥人
You wanna cross the U.S. Border with an undocumented Mexican national
还有美国头号女通缉犯一起穿过美国边境吗
and a woman who had her own episode on America's Most Wanted?
我认识可以帮我们穿过边境的人
I know someone who can get us across.
是你信得过的人吗
Someone you trust?
是的  我叔叔
Yes. My uncle.
我们得弃车
Well, we need to ditch the car.
销声匿迹
Get off the grid.
你为什么要在乎她
Why do you care what happens to her?
女士们
Hey, ladies.
因为她就是曾经的我
Because I was her.
那感觉糟糕透了
And it sucks.
我们走
Let's go.
这样确实销声匿迹了
Well, this is off the grid, all right.
真希望没有这么多人
But I wish it wasn't so crowded here.
真希望你俩没这么白
Well, I wish you two weren't so white.
女士们  出发
Let's go, chicas.
谢谢
Gracias.
墨西哥城
拉西姆数据中心
英雄市
特卡马卡州
拉雷多市
德州
格雷丝  告诉我
Grace, tell me what happens
这一切是怎么破灭的
when this all falls apart.
什么都没发生
Nothing happens.
没有预警
There's no warning.
第一天  一切都停止了
Day one, everything just stops.
手机用不了  没有电  城市陷入黑暗
No phones, no power. Cities go dark.
格雷丝  待在原地
Grace, stay there.
他们告诉我们
They told us
我们必须离开
we had to leave,
知道一切恢复正常
just until things got back to normal.
但是再也没恢复正常
But normal was never coming back.
第二天
Day two,
他们发射了核武器
they launched nukes.
他们以为电磁脉冲打击能压制军团
They thought they could contain Legion with tactical EMP strikes.
到了第三天  整个世界都陷入了战争
And by day three, the whole world was at war.
数百万人死亡
Millions died.
然后等食物消耗完了
And then, when the food ran out,
数十亿死亡
billions.
几个人因为一罐桃子杀了我爸
Some men killed my dad over a can of peaches.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
在我们以为战争已经结束了时候
When we thought the worst was over,
军团开始猎杀幸存者
then Legion started to hunt survivors.
我们知道你有吃的  小家伙
We know you got food, kid.
交出来
Give it up.
之后的几年我都不知道自己怎么撑过来的
I don't know how I made it through the next few years.
我尽量不去想
I just try not to think about it.
但我很幸运
But I got lucky.
有人找到了我
Someone found me,
救了我
saved me,
然后我们开始反击
and then we started fighting back.
让我猜猜
And let me guess.
达妮生的孩子可以阻止这一切
Dani gives birth to the one man that can stop it.
-什么  -未来想要你死
- What? - The future wants you dead
跟想要我死的原因一样
for the same reason it wanted me dead.
但我只是个小人物
But I'm nothing. I'm nobody.
没错  你不是威胁
Yeah, you're not the threat.
你的子宫是
It's your womb.
好  暂时换个人当圣母玛利亚
Fine. Let someone else be Mother Mary for a while.
如果你是圣母玛利亚
If you're Mother Mary,
为什么我这么想揍你
why do I so wanna beat the shit outta you?
叔叔
达妮
Dani!
你好  我的小美女
你来这里干什么
我的客户都能安全穿过边境
My clients get across safely.
追求更好的生活
To a better life.
我和别人不同  不会让他们在沙漠里等死
I don't leave them to die in the desert as some others do.
你能帮我们穿过边境吗
Can you get us across the border?
抱歉  但外国佬通常不是我的客户
Forgive me, but gringas are not my usual clientele.
你们两个做了什么非法的事吗
You two do something illegal maybe?
达妮不愿说的事
Something my Dani doesn't wish to say?
叔叔  有个...
Tio, there's...
这事听起来很疯狂
This is going to sound crazy,
但外面有个机器
but there's a machine out there.
机器人
A robot.
它杀死了爸爸和迭戈
It's what killed Papi and Diego,
还想要杀我
and it wants to kill me.
我们得摆脱它
We have to get away from it.
这理由挺新鲜
That's a new one.
格雷丝也算半个机器人
Grace is part machine, too.
这边走  女士们
This way, ladies.
无人机
作战与空中监控
禁区
你们好
Hey, fellas.
你好
What's up?
是不是和边境巡逻一模一样
Ain't that just like the Border Patrol.
迟到了五分钟  而且没给我们带甜甜圈
Five minutes late, and neglects to bring us donuts.
泰伦斯  闭嘴吧
Terrance, shut the fuck up.
你不想知道在追我们的是什么吗
达妮  我是个偷渡蛇头
总有人在追我
格里芬33接触
Griffin 33 in contact with
格林桥正西方的交叉路口
intersection due west of the Greene Bridge.
911  格里芬33遵命
9-11 Griffin 33 wilco.
格里芬33  911  那就是目标
Griffin 33 9-11, that is your target.
快到了
Almost there.
还有一公里到河边
One more kilometer to the river.
等等
Wait.
找掩护
Take cover.
上面有无人机
There's a drone up there.
我什么都没听到
I don't hear anything.
当然了  你又不是来自未来的
Yeah, well, you're not an augmented super soldier
强化超级士兵  对吧
from the future, are you?
我们得快点
We have to hurry.
请注意  所有巡逻队
Attention, all patrols.
请注意  现在通知最新坐标
Be advised, new coordinates issued.
嫌疑人此刻位于
Suspects are now 220 meters south
7B检查站以南220米处
of Checkpoint 7-Bravo.
已知他们是锡那罗亚贩毒集团的成员
They are known members of the Sinaloa Cartel.
美国与墨西哥当局都在通缉他们
Wanted by American and Mexican authorities.
预计他们携有武器  十分危险
They should be considered armed and dangerous.
允许致命打击
Deadly force is authorized.
到墙边之后
When you reach the wall,
下面有一扇门
there's a door beneath.
弗拉科会为你们带路
Flacco will show you the way.
我先过去
I will go first.
该死
Oh, shit.
站住  美国边境巡逻
Stop! U.S. Border Patrol.
把武器扔到地上
Put your weapons on the ground.
如果我们被关起来  它来找她  她就死定了
We get locked up, it comes for her, she's dead.
我不会再说一遍
I'm not gonna tell you again!
把武器扔到地上
Put them on the ground!
好的
Okay.
达妮  达妮
Dani! Dani!
他们可以射杀我  但我不能看着你们死掉
They can shoot me, but I'm not watching you die.
没事的
It's okay.
如果他们把我和她分开了
If they separate me from her,
-请把她救出去  -好的
- please get her out of there. - All right.
向前走  远离你们的武器
Walk forward and away from your weapons.
跪下
Get on the ground!
起来  走
Get up, move it.
-绑好了吗  -好了
- You get them? - Yep.
长官  那女孩是我的孙女
她受伤了  我需要陪着她
已拘捕一名男性嫌疑人
We have one male suspect
与三名女性嫌疑人
and three female suspects in custody.
达妮
Dani!
我们需要援助
We need help here!
美国边境巡逻拘留中心
德州  拉雷多
抱歉  但我没空听你废话
Sorry, but I don't have time for this shit.
而且这也不是我的问题
And it's not my problem.
我需要基本信息
I need basic information.
姓名  年龄  国籍
Name, age, country of origin.
这是真的  警官  我发誓
It's the truth, ma'am. I swear it.
这个机器杀死了我弟弟和我父亲
This machine, it killed my brother and my father,
它现在还想杀我
and now it wants to kill me,
他...
and he...
拜托  警官  请相信我
Please! Officer, you have to believe me.
你也有危险
You're in danger, too.
不  我在审核中心
No. I'm in Processing.
等你回到你来的地方之后
You ought to save your story
再讲你的故事吧  宝贝
till you get where you're going, honey.
心率有些高
Heart rate slightly elevated.
肺部没问题  来看一下伤口
Lungs are clear. Let's get that wound exposed.
气管无偏移
Trachea's midline.
检查一下有没有刺穿伤口
Let's check for any exit wounds.
搜身搜得挺好啊  兄弟们
Nice body search, fellas.
这是什么
What is that?
我从没见过类似的东西
I've never seen anything like this.
拍些照片吧
Let's get some pictures.
已确认  已经派人监视了  继续
That's confirmed. We have eyes on it now. Go ahead.
我被临时派来接一名刚收押的被拘留者
I just got TDY'd here to pick up a new detainee.
他们被关在哪
Where they being held?
去行政警官那里签到
Check in with the desk sergeant.
-他会指示你的  -谢谢
- He'll direct you. - Thank you.
晚上好
Evenin'.
我来接一名被拘留者  达妮·拉莫斯
Supposed to pick up a detainee. Dani Ramos.
请寄存你的武器
Please locker your weapon.
她经受了什么
What's been done to her?
她身体里这么多东西是怎么活下来的
How is she even alive with all this stuff in her?
我保证警报器会响  老兄
Expect a big ping, brother.
我的全身就是一件武器
My whole body's a weapon.
留着给女士讲去吧
Save it for the ladies.
抱歉  金属髋骨
Sorry. Metal hip.
两次阿富汗驻派
Two tours in Afghanistan.
好的  感谢你为国家效力
All right. Thank you for your service.
康纳
Connor.
莎拉·康纳
Sarah Connor.
我是里格比警官
I'm Officer Rigby.
幸会
It's an honor.
知道吗
Guess what.
你很有名
You're famous.
我们这里抓到的名人可不多
And we don't get a lot of famous around here.
走吧
Let's go.
你有自己的单人牢房
You belong in your own private cage.
我也想去
I want to go, too!
抓住她
Catch her!
我允许你们看我的私处了吗
Did I say you can look at my private parts?
新来的囚犯都被关在哪
Where do they take the new prisoners?
应该叫被拘留者  我们...
They're called detainees and we...
他们被送到了最南边的扣押区  等待审核...
They're taken to the south end holding area for processing...
谢谢
Thanks.
火警
这边走  女士
Right this way, ma'am.
我们的高级居住区在二楼
Our senior living section is on the second floor.
格雷丝  格雷丝
Grace! Grace!
-你还好吗  -他来了  我们得走了
- You okay? - He's here. We gotta go.
回来  大家都回来
Get back! Everybody, get back!
快点
Come on.
上去
Get in!
我们得走了
We gotta go.
莎拉来了  她来了
There's Sarah. She's coming.
-没时间了  -什么
- There's no time. - What?
不  我不会丢下她
No! I'm not leaving her!
达妮
Dani!
莎拉  快跑
Sarah, run!
-莎拉  带上她  -上去
- Sarah, get her! - Get in!
达妮  你需要明白
Dani, you need to understand something.
你不能再做这样的傻事了
You can't do stupid shit like that.
你不能拿自己的命冒险
You cannot put yourself at risk.
-他本会杀了莎拉  -那不重要
- He would have killed Sarah. - That doesn't matter!
你什么时候才会明白
When are you gonna get it?
如果你活不下来  所有人都会死
Everybody dies if you don't make it.
她说得对
She's right.
什么
What?
你们好
Hey there, fellas.
你们都是来看闹剧的吗
Y'all come to see the shitshow?
到底发生了什么
What the hell happened here?
被拘留者趁机逃脱  打开了所有的牢房
Detainee got loose, unlocked all the cages,
发生了混乱
just chaos from there.
不瞒你说
I don't mind tellin' you,
刚才五分钟里我把这辈子的祈祷都做了
I prayed more in five minutes than I have my whole life.
明白了
Heard that.
打听一下  你们知道哪能搞到直升机吗
Say, you boys know where I can get my hands on a chopper?
我们在坐标上方
We're over the coordinates.
距离一公里处着陆
Land a klick short.
卡尔窗饰
我们从不让你空窗
卡尔吗  这就是你的计划
So, Carl? That's the plan?
卡尔就是那个神秘发信人
Carl's the mystery texter.
不
No!
莎拉·康纳
Sarah Connor.
莎拉
Sarah!
我要杀了你  我要杀了你
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
你他妈在做什么
What the fuck are you doing?
-把枪给我  -不
- Let me have it! - No.
莎拉  你得冷静下来
Sarah, you need to calm down.
那东西杀了约翰
That thing killed John!
-是真的吗  -是
- Is that true? - Yes.
但我不是你想的那样
But I'm not what you think I am.
我要杀了你  你这混蛋
I'll kill you, you motherfucker!
莎拉  莎拉
Sarah, Sarah.
-要是这个人能帮我们  -他不是人类
- If this man can help us... - Not a man.
是终结者
A Terminator.
朝他脸上来一枪  看看他身体里什么
Shoot him in the face and see what's underneath!
我不在乎他是什么
I don't care what he is!
拜托了
Please.
-所以你是  -对
- So you're a... - Yes.
生化人系统101型
Cyberdyne Systems Model 101.
我能问问你的身份吗
May I ask what you are?
不能
No.
莎拉
Sarah?
我一张约翰的照片都没有
I don't have a photograph of John.
我从没拍过
I never took any.
我以为
I thought that...
如果他们不知道他的样貌
they couldn't find him...
就无法找到他
if they didn't know what he looked like.
但我现在快忘了他的长相了
But now I'm forgetting his face.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
为什么那姑娘被盯上了
So why is the girl targeted?
你不用知道
You don't need to know.
起码告诉我你是怎么找到我的吧
Well, can you at least tell me how you found me?
谁给你的坐标
Who gave you that?
谢谢
Thanks.
-请坐下  -废话少说
- Please sit down. - Cut the shit.
不错的一家
Nice family.
她也是终结者吗
She a Terminator, too?
那是你的终结者小孩吗
That's your little Terminator kid?
他叫马特奥
His name is Mateo.
我杀死约翰几个月后
I met his mother, Alicia,
遇到了马特奥的母亲艾丽西亚
a few months after I killed John.
你不准提他的名字
Oh, you don't get to say his name.
永远不准
Ever.
她的丈夫虐打她
Her husband had beaten her.
企图杀了她儿子
He was trying to kill her child.
她无处可去
She had nowhere to go.
照顾这个家庭给了我生活目标
Caring for this family gave me purpose.
没有目标  我们就什么也不是
'Cause without purpose, we are nothing.
感人的故事  你到底想说什么
Touching story. Does it have a point?
抚养我的儿子  马特奥时
While raising Mateo, my son,
我开始理解我从你那里夺走了什么
I began to understand what I had taken from you.
什么  你逐渐生出了良心
Wait. You grew a conscience?
差不多的东西吧  对
The equivalent of one, yes.
它是个潜入者
It's an infiltrator.
它在撒谎
It's lying.
我的任务完结后  就没有别的指令了
When my mission was completed, there were no further orders.
因此在二十年间  我不断地学习
So for 20 years, I kept learning
如何变得更像人类
how to become more human.
那些信息呢
So what about the texts?
时间错位一旦发生
When chronal displacement occurs
在错位事件之前
there's a shockwave through time
会出现一道时间上可测量的震荡波
measurable before the event.
这是方法  不是原因
That's how, not why.
为了给你目标  莎拉
To give you purpose, Sarah.
我想这样你儿子的死就有意义了
I thought it would bring meaning to your son's death.
你知道怎样让我儿子的死有意义吗
You know what would give meaning to his death?
不  莎拉
No, Sarah!
这将很难对艾丽西亚解释
This will be very hard to explain to Alicia.
它是个终结者
It's a Terminator!
而我们正在同一个终结者开战
And we are fighting a Terminator.
一个我们无法抵挡的终结者
One that we can't stop.
你相信命运吗  莎拉
Do you believe in fate, Sarah?
还是说  你相信我们每分每秒所做的决定
Or do you believe that we all can change the future
都能够改变未来
every second by every choice that we make?
你选择了改变未来
You chose to change the future.
你选择了毁灭天网
You chose to destroy Skynet.
你给了我自由
You set me free.
现在
And now,
我会帮你保护那女孩
I'm going to help you protect the girl
因为我选择如此
because I choose to.
是艾丽西亚回来了
That's Alicia.
她需要我帮忙把买的菜拿进来
She needs my help with the groceries.
-你好  宝贝  -你好
- Hi, honey. - Hi.
家里来客人了
We have company.
客人  是谁
Company? Who?
热水足够吗
Was there enough hot water?
-足够  谢谢  -谢谢
- Yes, thank you. - Thanks.
给
Here you go.
卡尔  你的朋友看起来饿了
Carl, your friends look hungry.
你想吃点三明治或者薯片之类的吗
Would you like some sandwiches and chips or something?
这主意不错  艾丽西亚
That's a great idea, Alicia.
马特奥  去帮你妈妈吧
Mateo, why don't you go and help your mother?
好的  爸  我这就去
Sure, Dad. I'm on it.
所以你是卡尔
So, you're Carl.
大家都这么叫我
That's what everyone calls me, yes.
我他妈永远不会叫你卡尔
I'm never gonna fucking call you Carl.
他们不知道吗
They don't know?
-是的  -她没注意你体重超过180公斤吗
- No. - She hasn't noticed that you weigh 400 pounds?
也没发现你从来不睡觉吗
That you never sleep?
我们不是肉体关系
Our relationship is not physical.
我换尿布麻利又不抱怨
She appreciated that I could change diapers.
她喜欢这个
Efficiently and without any complaints.
我很可靠  我擅长倾听
I am reliable, I'm a very good listener
我还非常幽默
and I'm extremely funny.
行
Okay.
我们要怎么阻止这东西
How do we stop this thing?
我们选好我们的武器和场地
We choose our weapons and our ground,
设置一个杀戮陷阱
we set up a kill box,
然后用达妮引它过来
and then we use Dani to bring it to us.
-什么  -然后干掉它
- What? - And then we take it down.
不  不行  达妮不能当诱饵
No. No way. Dani is not bait.
莎拉说得对
Sarah is right.
我们的一个战略优势就是
Our one tactical advantage
终结者眼里只有任务
is that the Terminator only sees its mission.
达妮去哪里他就跟去哪里
Wherever Dani goes, he will follow.
的确如此  我会等着他来
Damn right it will. And I will be there.
我不会让她给你们冒险当诱饵的
Well, I'm not about to stake her out like some goat for you.
那你有什么计划  接着逃跑吗
What's your plan? More running?
我的计划是把她藏起来  即便藏到矿井下面
My plan is to hide her at the bottom of a mineshaft if I have to.
-至少藏到我  -别吵了
- At least until I... - Just stop it!
我不会藏到矿井底下
I'm not hiding at the bottom of a mineshaft.
我拒绝在恐惧中度过余生
I'm not gonna live in fear the rest of my life.
即使你的计划意味着我命不久矣
Even if your plan means that might not be long.
我要挺身反抗
I want to stand and fight.
我们选好我们的武器
So, we choose our weapons
以及场地
and our ground.
我们要设置一个
We're gonna set up a...
-杀戮陷阱  -杀戮陷阱
- Kill box. - Kill box.
然后  用我做诱饵
And then, we're gonna use me as bait.
然后  我们杀掉那东西
And then, we kill that thing.
行吗
Okay?
这计划成功率很高
This plan has a high probability of success.
行
Okay.
有什么武器
What weapons?
你一直备着这些东西吗
You just keep these around?
即便不被失控的人工智能统治
Even without a rogue AI taking over,
我计算过  人类的文明
I calculate a 74% chance
也有74%的概率会毁灭  重归野蛮
that human civilization will collapse into barbarism.
到了那个最终的时刻
And in that eventuality,
这些武器会是保护我的家人的关键
these weapons will be vital to protect my family.
况且
Also...
这里是德州
this is Texas.
开始  连射
Go. Rapid fire.
你要试着缓解后坐力
You're anticipating the recoil.
重心前移  手臂举高
Put your weight forward, arms up.
腿再站开一点
And wider stance.
手肘不要绷得太紧
Don't lock out your elbows.
废话够了
Enough of this bullshit.
我们来动真格的
Let's get serious.
一个终结者刚刚杀了你全家
A Terminator has just killed your whole family.
你要怎么做
What do you do?
你知道这些枪杀不死它
You know these guns won't kill it.
只能拖慢它
They'll only slow him down.
根据你对他能力的描述
According to your description of his capabilities,
我们最好的选择就是弄到一把军用能量武器
our best option is to secure a military-grade energy weapon.
EMP吗
An EMP?
那是什么
What is that?
电磁脉冲
An electromagnetic pulse.
如果我们近距离使用
If we had one close range,
能摧毁Rev-9
it would fry a Rev-9.
我或许认识一人
I might know a guy.
宾厄姆的空军情报官
Air Force intelligence officer out of Bingham.
离这里151公里
It's 94 miles from here.
我们今天下午就出发
We should leave this afternoon.
好的
Okay.
你一直在跟踪我吗
You've been tracking me?
如果你要把手机放在薯片袋里
If you want to keep your phone in a bag of potato chips,
那就别拿出来
then keep your phone in a bag of potato chips.
-照顾好妈妈  -我会的
- Take good care of Mama. - I will.
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
你跟他们说了什么
What did you tell them?
我告诉他们你们的到来  让这个地方不安全了
I told them you coming here makes this place unsafe for them.
而且  我曾警告他们可能会来的那一天
Also, the day I warned them might come,
已经到来
has come.
我的过去来找我算账了
My past has caught up with me.
还有
And...
我不会回来了
I won't be back.
你爱他们吗
Do you love them?
不是人类的爱
Not like a human can.
多年来我一直认为这是种优势
For many years I thought it was an advantage.
但不是的
It isn't.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我只是想告诉你
I just want you to know
等达妮安全了  这一切都结束后
that when Dani's safe and this is all over,
我会杀了你
I am going to kill you.
我明白
I understand.
这不仅仅是要选对颜色
There's much more to it than just picking the right color.
还要考虑的是质感  材料的重量
It's the texture, the weight of the material.
-一个错误的选择  -莎拉  你还好吗
- One wrong choice... - Sarah, you okay?
会破坏整个房间的观感
it can destroy the look of the entire room.
-好吧  -之前有一个客户来找我
- Fine. - There was this one customer that came to me.
他想在一个小女孩的房间里挂上纯色窗帘
He wanted to have solid-color drapes in a little girl's room.
我说  "千万别"
I said, "Don't do it."
你需要蝴蝶  圆点  气球
You need butterflies, polka dots, balloons.
别动
Stay put.
总是很高兴见到你  少校
Always good to see you, Major.
见到你一点都不高兴  康纳
It's never good to see you, Connor.
你给我带了生日礼物吗
You got my birthday present?
你知道的  莎拉
You know, Sarah,
我不会随便为一个人犯叛国罪
I don't commit treason for just anybody.
这个电磁脉冲对四级强度目标的
What's the range of the EMP
射程是多少
against a Class Four hardened target?
保镖吗
Bodyguard?
我是做窗帘的
I do drapes.
他是我行动小组的一员
He's part of my operations team.
而且他应该把嘴闭好
And he should just shut the fuck up.
少校  宾厄姆有哪种直升机
Major, what kind of helos fly out of Bingham?
黑鹰和支努干  怎么了
Black Hawks and Chinooks. Why?
他找到我们了
He's found us.
找掩护
Take cover!
少校
Major!
我们都上车了  快走
We're in. Go.
往基地开  沿着这条路走大约三公里
Head for the base. About two miles down this road.
它马上就会追过来
It'll be on us again in a minute.
我是迪恩少校
This is Major Dean,
第361情报监视侦察小组
361st Intelligence, Surveillance, and Reconnaissance Group.
宣布进入一级战备
Declaring ThreatCon Delta.
我在宾厄姆空军基地以南
I'm currently two miles south
三公里的白色面包车上
of Bingham Air Base in a white van.
正向西门行驶
Headed for the west gate.
敌方正驾驶被盗的警用直升机追赶
Pursued by hostiles in a stolen police helicopter.
我们要去哪里
Where are we going?
那些士兵不能帮助我们吗
Can't all those soldiers back there help us?
他们能拖慢它  但杀不掉它
They'll be able to slow it down, but they can't kill it.
C-5货机
The C-5.
你能开吗
Can you fly that?
当然可以
Of course.
你正在进入未经许可的领空
You are entering unauthorized airspace.
立刻掉头  否则我们就开火了
Turn around now or we will open fire.
准备好
Get ready.
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
别碍事
Stand down!
这些人是地区承包商  友军
These people are district contractors. Friendlies.
我会尽我所能掩护你们
I'll do what I can to cover your backs
直至你们能起飞
until you can get airborne.
他们没有获得授权  拦住他们
Hey, they're not clear! Stop 'em!
扫描模式
匹配模式
威胁分析
扫描层级
分辨率调整
威胁识别
优先级超控
威胁评估:紧迫
坐标方位
威胁类型
飞行路径
我们又被他锁定了
We have been reacquired.
找掩护
Take cover!
别碰我
Don't touch me.
我没子弹了
I'm out.
卡尔
Carl!
抱歉破坏了你的小屋
Sorry about your shed.
舰桥42  这里是毒蛇16  保持警惕
Bridge 42, this is Viper 16. Stay in tension.
希望他们不会把我们打下来
Hopefully they won't shoot us down.
神鹰行动  这是毒蛇16
Noble Eagle Ops, this is Viper 16.
我们去哪里
Where are we going?
之后再想
Figuring that out next.
但那些悍马车可以直接降落伞着陆
But those Humvees are rigged for parachute landing,
我们可以着陆后
so we can punch out
找个偏僻的地方使用电磁脉冲
and then find some remote spot to use the EMP.
有麻烦了
We have a problem.
那  如果我们不用这个跟他打  能赢吗
So... if we fight him without those, can we win?
基于我们现有的武器  我估计胜算是12%
Based on the weapons we have, I estimate our chances at 12%.
那也不是毫无胜算啊
That's not zero.
也好不到哪里去
It's not much better.
那我们就去找更多的武器
Then we have to find some more weapons
我们按计划行事
and we stick to the plan.
-我们设陷阱然后就能  -不  达妮  不行
- We set the trap and then we can... - No, Dani, you can't do that.
为什么
Why?
因为我儿子会拯救我们所有人吗
Because my son is supposed to save us all?
在那之前呢
And until then, what?
我们就眼睁睁看着人们死去吗
We just keep watching people die?
人类的未来取决于你成功...
The future of the human race depends on you making it...
我才不管什么未来
I don't give a shit about the future.
又或者是我将来某天会做什么
Or what I'm maybe supposed to do someday.
重要的是我们现在做出的选择
What matters are the choices we make now.
这种表情我以前见过太多次了
I've seen that look too many times before.
你认识我
You knew me.
在未来
In the future.
是的
Yeah.
我认识你
I know you.
是你
It was you...
在审判日之后的废墟中找到了我
who found me in the ruins after Judgment Day.
你救了我
You saved me.
猎杀者
HKs.
开枪啊  十秒内我们都会死
Shoot me, and we'll all be dead in 10 seconds.
军团就想要我们这样
This is what Legion wants us to do.
自相残杀
Kill each other.
我们应该和机器战斗
We should be fighting the machines.
有什么意义  我们赢不了的
What's the point? We can't win.
军团是人类创造的
Legion didn't exist until humans created it.
那东西是我们制造的
We made that thing.
我们就能摧毁它
We can destroy it.
就因为机器要我们躺下等死
Are we supposed to lie down and die
我们就应该照做吗
because some machine decided it?
那就是我们的命运吗
Is that our fate?
那去他的命运
Well, fuck fate.
你叫什么
What's your name?
格雷丝
Grace.
我叫达妮娜
I'm Daniella.
达妮
Dani.
你救了我
You saved me
你养育了我
and you raised me,
你教会了我希望
and you taught me to hope.
就像你拯救并教会其他人一样
Like you saved and taught the others.
你把拾荒者变成了民兵
You turned scavengers into militias
把民兵又变成了军队
and militias into an army.
我们在灰烬中重生  夺回了我们的世界
We rose up out of the ashes and we took our world back.
你教会我们
You taught us
命运不是注定的
there is no fate
而是自己创造的
but what we make for ourselves.
达妮
Dani,
你不是未来某个救世主的母亲
you are not the mother of some man who saves the future.
你就是未来
You are the future.
所以军团要追杀你
That's why Legion wants you dead.
她就是约翰
She's John.
你就是约翰
You're John.
抱歉之前没告诉你
I'm sorry I didn't tell you this before.
但你说我将会见到的过去的达妮
But you told me that the Dani I'd meet in the past
无法接受这个现实
couldn't handle it.
但你不再是那个达妮了
But you're not that Dani anymore.
DE12
Delta Echo 12.
这里是KC-320
This is KC-320.
加油准备就绪
Ready to refuel.
收到请回答
Acknowledge.
收到  KC-320  但你是不是来早了
Copy that, KC-320, but aren't you a bit early?
他来了
It's him.
我们得走了  快
We gotta go. Now.
上悍马车坐好
Strap in to the Humvee.
格雷丝
Grace!
自动驾驶仪开启
达妮
Dani!
操
Fuck.
打开货舱
Open the cargo bay.
地面货舱门
我去找莎拉
I'll get Sarah!
-莎拉  开门啊  -卡住了
- Sarah! The door? - It's jammed!
弄断绳子
Get the straps.
操
Shit!
怎么回事
What's happening?
格雷丝  她人呢
Grace! Where is she?
我没看见她
I don't see her.
操
Fuck.
再来两个  他们要运进来了
Got two more. They're bringing 'em in.
你们看
Guys!
什么情况
What the shit?
天呐  格雷丝
Oh, my God! Grace.
-我以为你死了  -我们降落得太快了
- I thought you were dead. - We're dropping too fast.
三  二  一
Three, two, one!
-天呐  -操
- My God! - Oh, shit!
达妮  快下车
Dani, get out.
-挡住了  -要掉下去了
- It's blocked! - It's not gonna hold!
坚持住
Hold on!
不
No!
莎拉
Sarah?
-怎么了  -我的肩膀
- What is it? - My shoulder.
脱臼了
It's dislocated.
你还会看病啊
So you're a doctor now?
操
Fuck!
他来了  我们不能待在这里
He's coming. We can't stay here.
该死
Shit.
她在做什么
What is she doing?
不不  格雷丝  真要这样吗
No, no, Grace. Really?
系好安全带
Strap in!
是啊  不然多危险
Right. Otherwise it could be dangerous.
找找车灯开关
Try to find the lights.
趴下
Get down!
后座有降落伞  拿过来
There's a parachute back there. Grab it.
我们可以缠住他
We can tangle him up.
听我说
Listen to me.
等它出现  你就拉这条绳子
It comes, you pull this cord.
这条绳子
This cord.
然后你绕过它浮上水面
And then you swim past it up to the surface.
好
Okay.
格雷丝
Grace.
它在哪里
Where is it?
我不知道  我没看到
I don't know. I lost him.
我们不能待在这里
We can't stay here.
我们得走了
We gotta go.
好
All right.
你能走上去吗
Can you make it up there?
我不知道
I don't know.
锁住了
It's locked.
我来试试
Let me try.
格雷丝
Grace.
等等
Wait.
或许有其他门
There's maybe another door.
靠
Shit.
格雷丝
Grace!
达妮  快跑
Dani, you have to run.
-你快跑  我们保护不了你  -什么
- You have to run. We can't protect you. - What?
这里只有我还能作战
I'm the only one of us who can still throw a punch.
还有一件武器
There's another weapon.
是什么
What?
我的电源
My power source.
我们要怎么取出来才不会害死你
How do we get it out of you without killing you?
-做不到  -那就不行
- You can't. - No!
怎么回事
What?
你看起来糟透了
You look terrible.
至少我的脸还是完整的
At least I still have all my face.
你把这个落在飞机上了
You left this on the plane.
我打不开那扇门
I can't get through that door.
快  快
Come on! Hurry!
我们得赶快走
We have to move.
他离我们不远
He's not far behind.
不
No.
我们就在这里决一死战
We make our stand here.
这里就是我们的杀戮陷阱
This is our kill box.
达妮
Dani.
我不会再逃跑了
I'm not running!
把女孩交给我
Give me the girl.
不
No.
你真该听我的
You really should.
你和我为同一个目标而生
You and I were built for the same purpose.
而军团是唯一的未来
And Legion is the only future.
我就来自那样一个未来
I came from a future like that.
一个失败的未来
It failed.
我知道你和她素不相识
I know she's a stranger to you.
何不把她交给我呢
Why not just let me have her?
因为我们不是机器  冷血混蛋
Because we're not machines, you metal motherfucker.
格雷丝
Grace!
来抓我
I'm over here!
闪开
Move.
莎拉
Sarah!
闪开
Move!
格雷丝在哪
Where's Grace?
我不知道
I don't know.
她在那边
Oh, there she is.
格雷丝  格雷丝
Grace! Grace!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
格雷丝
Grace.
莎拉
Sarah!
它还没死
It's not dead.
等等  我们得带你离开这里
Wait. We gotta take you out of here.
好吗  格雷丝  我们走
Okay? Grace, let's go.
我的电源
My power source.
靠近它  电源就能毁了它的神经网络
Get it close, and it'll fry his neural net.
格雷丝...
Grace...
我做不到
I can't.
不  你可以
Yes, you can.
达妮
Dani.
你把我派来就为了这一刻
This is what you sent me here to do.
不
No.
我们都知道  我回不去了
We both knew I wasn't coming back.
-我做不到  -达妮  拜托
- I can't. - Dani, please.
你救了我
You saved me.
这次让我救你
Let me save you.
-拜托  -不
- Please. - No.
动手吧
You do it.
快动手  达妮
Do it, Dani.
对不起  格雷丝
I'm sorry, Grace.
我一点也不遗憾
I'm not.
你夺走了我的一切  混蛋
现在...
我要杀了你  混蛋
I'm gonna kill you, fucker.
起来
Get up!
帮帮她
Help her!
该死的
God damn it...
卡尔
Carl!
快醒醒
Wake up!
为了约翰
For John.
能源水平
系统指标
运作20
错误992
全部54768个部位系统错误
神经网络崩溃
即将关闭
最低临界值
I/O  204
功能  0
即将关闭
环境温度过载
系统危急
我们打败它了  格雷丝
We got him, Grace.
你救了我
You saved me.
格雷丝
Grace!
格雷丝  快来  宝贝
Grace, come on, honey.
我们该走了
It's time to go.
快来  你们俩
Come on, you two.
拿上自己的东西  小家伙们
Grab your stuff, you guys.
我不会再让她为我牺牲
I won't let her die for me again.
那你得做好准备了
Then you need to be ready.